<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../../Schema/songSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <info>
        <title>Seventy Times 7</title>
        <album>Your Favorite Weapon</album>
        <tempo meas="BPM">91</tempo>
        <key>A Major</key>
        <songWriter>Jesse Lacey</songWriter>
        <composer>Jesse Lacey</composer>
        <producer>Mike Sapone</producer>
        <label>Triple Crown</label>
        <released>2001-10-09</released>
        <recorded from="2001" to="2001">2001</recorded>
        <songLength>00:03:34</songLength>
    </info>
    <lyrics>
        <verse n="1"><line>Back in <ref img="school">school</ref> they never <ref img="school">taught</ref> us what we needed to know,</line>
        <line>like how to deal with despair, or someone <ref type="idiom">breaking your heart</ref>.</line>
        <line>For twelve <ref img="time">years</ref> I've <ref type="idiom">held it all together</ref> but a <ref img="time">night</ref> like this is begging to <ref type="idiom">pull me
            apart</ref>.</line>
        <line>I played it quiet, left you deep in conversation.</line>
        <line>I felt uncool and hung out around the kitchen.</line>
        <line>I remember I kept thinking that I know you never would,</line>
        <line>and now I know I want to kill you like only a best friend could.</line>
</verse>
        <chorus>
            <line>Everyone's <ref type="idiom">caught on</ref> to everything you do</line>
            <line>Everyone's <ref type="idiom">caught on</ref> to.</line>
        </chorus>

        <verse n="2">
            <line>As if this happening wasn't enough I got to go</line>
            <line>and write a song just to remind myself how bad it sucked.</line>
            <line>Ignore the sun, the cover's over my head.</line>
            <line>I wrote a message on my <ref img="bed">pillow</ref> that says, "<ref type="bandMember">Jesse</ref>, stay <ref img="bed">asleep in bed</ref>."</line>
            <line>So don't apologize. I hope you choke and die.</line>
            <line>Search your cell for something with which to <ref img="suicide">hang yourself</ref>.</line>
            <line>They say you need to <ref type="rel">pray if you want to go to heaven</ref></line>
            <line>but they don't tell you what to say when your whole life has gone to <ref type="rel">hell</ref>.</line>
        </verse>

        <chorus>
            <line>Everyone's caught on to everything you do</line>
            <line>Everyone's caught on to</line>
            <line>And everyone's caught on to everything you do (And I can't let you, let me down
                again.)</line>
            <line>Everyone's caught on to (And I can't let you, let me down again)</line>
        </chorus>

        <bridge>
            <line>So, is that what you call a getaway?</line>
            <line>Tell me what you got away with.</line>
            <line>Cause I've seen more spine in jellyfish.</line>
            <line>I've seen more guts in eleven-year-old kids.</line>
            <line>Have another drink and drive yourself home.</line>
            <line>I hope there's ice on all the roads.</line>
            <line>And you can think of me when you forget your seatbelt,</line>
            <line>and again when your head goes through the windshield.</line>
        </bridge>

        <bridge>
            <line>And is that what you call tact?</line>
            <line>You're as subtle as a brick in the small of my back.</line>
            <line>So let's end this call, and end this conversation.</line>
            <line>and is that what you call a getaway?</line>
            <line>well tell me what you got away with.</line>
            <line>cause you left the frays from the ties you severed</line>
            <line>when you say best friends means friends forever</line>
        </bridge>

        <bridge>
            <line>So, is that what you call a getaway?</line>
            <line>Well tell me what you got away with.</line>
            <line>Cause I've seen more spine in jellyfish.</line>
            <line>I've seen more guts in eleven-year-old kids.</line>
            <line>Have another drink and drive yourself home.</line>
            <line>I hope there's ice on all the roads.</line>
            <line>And you can think of me when you forget your seatbelt,</line>
            <line>and again when your head goes through the windshield.</line>
        </bridge>

        <chorus>
            <line>Everyone's caught on to everything you do (And I can't let you, let me down
                again)</line>
            <line>Everyone's caught on to (And I can't let you, let me down again)</line>
            <line>And everyone's caught on to everything you do (And I can't let you, let me down
                again)</line>
            <line>Everyone's caught on to (And I can't let you, let me down again)</line>
        </chorus>
    </lyrics>
</song>
