<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../../Schema/songSchema.rnc" type="application/relax-ng-compact-syntax"?>
<song>
    <info>
        <title>Sudden Death In Carolina</title>
        <album>Your Favorite Weapon</album>
        <tempo meas="BPM">167</tempo>
        <key>D Major</key>
        <songWriter>Jesse Lacey</songWriter>
        <composer>Jesse Lacey</composer>
        <producer>Mike Sapone</producer>
        <label>Triple Crown</label>
        <released>2001-10-09</released>
        <recorded from="2001" to="2001">2001</recorded>
        <songLength>00:03:02</songLength>
    </info>
    <lyrics>
        <verse n="1">
            <line>Last night I swallowed liquor and a lighter and this morning I threw up
                fire.</line>
            <line>But it's nothing new. I've been piecing it together and it's got something to
                do</line>
            <line>with every look thrown like a knife across a crowded room.</line>
            <line>Every slow and quiet car ride I spent drinking in the backseat.</line>
            <line>Every stupid melody to every stupid song.</line>
            <line>And every stupid word that everybody's hanging on.</line>
        </verse>

        <chorus>
            <line>What difference does this difference in age make?</line>
            <line>I know how it ends... she'll kill me quick.</line>
            <line>So call 911.</line>
            <line>I'm already dead but someone should be caught</line>
            <line>and held responsible for this bloody mess.</line>
        </chorus>

        <verse n="2">
            <line>Last night I fell asleep next to a liar and I woke up with a shiner.</line>
            <line>And it's all that I remember from a night spent lying on my back</line>
            <line>with a view of a stone white ceiling and the back of your head.</line>
            <line>This dark and quiet bed felt like the middle of nowhere.</line>
            <line>We beat each other up just like we always do.</line>
            <line>When I'm talking to myself I'd always rather be talking to you.</line>
        </verse>

        <chorus>
            <line>What difference does this difference in age make?</line>
            <line>I know how it ends... she'll kill me quick.</line>
            <line>Call 911.</line>
            <line>I'm already dead but someone should be caught</line>
            <line>and held responsible for this bloody mess.</line>
        </chorus>

        <verse n="3">
            <line>Call homicide. Take the case to court.</line>
            <line>Her lips taste like a loaded gun</line>
            <line>and I'm her number one chalk outline on the floor.</line>

            <line>They hung her from the bridge on Monday.</line>
            <line>The gathering turned into a mob out on the lawn.</line>
            <line>They dropped her body in the river.</line>
            <line>And school and work returned to normal before long...</line>
        </verse>

        <chorus>
            <line>Call 911.</line>
            <line>I'm already dead but someone should be caught</line>
            <line>and held responsible for this bloody mess.</line>
            <line>Call homicide. Take the case to court.</line>
            <line>Her lips taste like a loaded gun</line>
            <line>and I'm her number one chalk outline on the floor.</line>
        </chorus>
    </lyrics>
</song>
