<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<song>
    <info>
        <title>Lit Me Up</title>
        <album>Science Fiction</album>
        <track n="1"/>
        <tempo/>
        <key></key>
        <songWriter>Brand New</songWriter>
        <composer/>
        <producer>Mike Sapone</producer>
        <label>Procrastinate! Music Traitors</label>
        <released>2017-17-08</released>
        <recorded from="2014" to="2014">2014</recorded>
        <songLength>00:06:17</songLength>
    </info>
    <lyrics>
        <line>This tape recounts a dream which occurred close to the termination of approximately
            400 hours of intensive, individual therapy. Now, the patient recounts her dream:</line>
        <line>I had this dream earlier this morning and I wrote it down. The dream is that I'm in
            some sort of a... and I'm in a hotel I'm at... I'm like at a convention or something.
            And I feel sort of almost like there's too much going on. There are all different kinds
            of meetings going on. Stuff on experimental psych and therapy, chemical aspects. All of
            it</line>
        <line>But, I'm... while I don't mind having all this going on inside of me. It's sort of...
            I think I'm going to be relieved when it's over. When I can sort of settle back
            down</line>
        <line>It's where you live, but you don't know how it's built</line>
        <line>If we're just dust, then it doesn't matter who you kill</line>
        <line>Don't cut me up and tell me that it's ok</line>
        <line>Just turn it off 'cause I don't care anyway</line>
        <line>It lit me up</line>
        <line>It lit me up</line>
        <line>It lit me up</line>
        <line>It lit me up</line>
        <line>Something's stirring in a deep Atlantic trench</line>
        <line>Doesn't forget the thousand years before it slept</line>
        <line>It's the beast, it's my heart, it's open</line>
        <line>Dive down into its unit in its head</line>
        <line>It lit me up</line>
        <line>It lit me up</line>
        <line>It lit me up</line>
        <line>It lit me up</line>
        <line>It lit me up like a torch on a pitch black night</line>
        <line>Like an ember in the needles of a dried out pine</line>
        <line>Lit me up and I burn from the inside out</line>
        <line>Yeah, I burn like a witch in a Puritan town</line>
        <line>It lit me</line>
        <line>It lit me</line>
        <line>When I grow up I want to be a heretic</line>
        <line>I want to climb over the wall 'cause I'm not on the list</line>
        <line>I want to put my hands to work till the work's done</line>
        <line>I want to open up my heart like the ocean</line>
        <line>It lit me up</line>
        <line>It lit me up</line>
        <line>It lit me up</line>
        <line>It lit me up</line>
        <line>It lit me up like a rag soaked in gasoline</line>
        <line>In the neck of the bottle breaking right at my feet</line>
        <line>It lit me up and I burned from the inside out</line>
        <line>Yeah, I burned like a witch in a Puritan town</line>
        <line>It lit me</line>
        <line>It was a good dream</line>
        <line>If so...you will be dead tonight</line>
    </lyrics>
</song>
